mumbai77.com 2016-10-23

# Mumbai77.com Privacy Policy

---|---  

* * *

The following Privacy Policy outline your obligations when using the Mumbai77 website. You can also review our Terms Of Use and Disclaimer, which outlines general terms and condition one must read before accessing the website for any purpose. 

  1. Google Ads

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the 

[_Network Advertising Initiative_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the 

[_NAI Self-Regulatory principles_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) for publishers (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time. 
  2. Online Payments

Mumbai77.com do not collect any credit card and related personal information accept mentioned in the registration and payment form which are required for a registered customers record. Although our payment gateway partner EBS take all the measures while processing the transaction, We do not gaurantee on any transaction and information leak which might happen due to various reasons like accessing and making payments from a publicly accessed machine like from cyber cafe which might have malicious software installed and is affected. We request users to do such transactions from personal pc's which are secured through proper firewall and anti-virus.

If you decide to visit Mumbai77 website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Maharastra state law at Mumbai High Court only. 
  3. Thanks Note

We thank all our registered users, visitors, comment and feedback providers for visiting Mumbai77.com. We also request you to Recommend this site to your friends and Relatives if you find this can help them in any ways. Please do visit again for updates. 

Top
